tppcrpg.net 2016-05-06

# Gorilla Nation - Evolve Privacy Policy

**GorillaNation.com** **(the “Site”)**

**  Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy was last modified on May 8, 2012. 

Evolve Media Corp., the owner and operator of GorillaNation.com (“Company,” “we,” or “us”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared.  This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Company when you use the Website and related services (the “Service”), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information.   We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Information We Collect 

**User-Provided Information:**   You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, when you register with the Service.  Also, you may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our Website.  If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. 

**Cookies Information:**   When you visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Company help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Website.  A cookie does not collect personal information about you.  Company uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

**Log File Information:**   Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page.  When you register with or view our Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. 

**Clear Gifs Information:**   When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously.  No personally identifiable information from your Company account is collected using these clear gifs.  In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.  The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make us better for our users. 

**New Technology:**   As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means and there may be other technologies present that act in a similar way but are protected by confidentiality. 

**How We Use Your Information**

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service (for instance, in User Content you post) becomes available to the public.  If you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content. 

By providing Company your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers.  If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by sending an email message to legal[at]EvolveMediaCorp.com with the word "No email" in the subject field.  Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. 

Company may use certain information about you and/or your User Content without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing advertisements and promotions. 

Company reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the Website. Company has the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation, if in its sole opinion, such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use Agreement or to protect or defend its rights or property or those of any third party.  Company also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party. 

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in. 

**How We Share Your Information**

**Personally Identifiable Information:  **Company will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others.  Company may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you.  If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy.  We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Company (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). 

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. 

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Company will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our Website; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Company, our users or others.  Please note we may not provide notice prior to disclosure in such cases. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:**  We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Company services. 

Company allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. 

Company does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Company to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The Company privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers. 

**How We Protect Your Information**

Company uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Company makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Company, at all times. 

**Compromise of Personal Information**

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Company will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law. 

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through Company, in which case Company may not be able to provide certain services to you.  

**Children's Privacy Policy**  
_General.   _Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Some of the promotions offered by Company may be directed in whole or in part to children under the age of 13. Generally, we do not directly or indirectly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13 in connection with these promotions. For some promotions, children are allowed to send preprogrammed messages to friends regarding a particular feature of the Website. In these instances, the child is prompted to enter the email addresses of his or her friends and some other non-identifiable information, such as his or her first name only. This information is automatically discarded as soon as the preprogrammed message is delivered. From time to time, however, we may request limited personally-identifiable information in order to conduct online contests or sweepstakes. Our practices with respect to collection of personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13 are described below. We do not condition a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to engage in the activity. In addition, a parent may at anytime review any personally-identifiable information collected about their child under the age of 13, have this information deleted and prohibit further collection or use of the child's information (although this may require the child to forfeit any prize won in a sweepstakes or contest). 

_Information Collected in Contests and Sweepstakes._ Company occasionally offers contests and/or sweepstakes on websites owned by Company or on third party websites directed in whole or in part to children under the age of 13. **Our contests and sweepstakes are designed in such a manner that a child under the age of 13 is not required to provide any personally- identifiable information about him/herself prior to being named a winner.** To participate in these contests or sweepstakes, however, we may require the child to provide a screen name and a parent's e-mail address. We send an email notification to the parent’s email address only if the child has been selected as a potential winner of the contest or sweepstakes. The parent must then respond to the email notification by the deadline provided in the email notification, and must also complete and submit any prize claim documents in accordance with any instructions provided by the Company or as set forth in the official rules for the contest or sweepstakes.

The parental email address collected from each child is used solely to notify the parent if his/her child is a potential winner of the contest or sweepstakes, and it is not provided to any third party except those third parties we have engaged to assist us in running the contest or sweepstakes. These third parties are required to maintain the parental email in confidence and may only use it in connection with the services they are providing to us. The information collected from winners may be (i) used in advertising and promotional activities relating to our contest and/or sweepstakes, which may include making certain of this information publicly available, and (ii) passed on to third parties for the purpose of awarding prizes, and, depending on the type of prize, these third parties may not be prohibited from using the information for purposes other than awarding the prize (such as marketing or advertising). **Again, please note that personally-identifiable information is only collected from the parents of children under the age of 13 who have potentially won a prize, and only after the parent consents to the award of the prize and the disclosure of the information**.

_Contact Information._   If you have any questions about our Children's Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at legal[at]evolvemediacorp.com. 

**Third Parties**

We expect our partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users.  Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our Website, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. 

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and outside the scope of this document. 

Links to Other Websites: We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website nor the information or content contained therein.  Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect.  User browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our Website, is subject to that other website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

**Third Party Advertisements and Technologies:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website as is explained in detail in our Website’s Terms of Use.  In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or other advertising technology may be placed on your browser.  This advertising technology uses information derived from your visits to the Website to target advertising within this Website.  This information is used for many purposes, for example, it helps us try to ensure that you do not see the same advertisements over and over again. We also use this information to help select and display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you (sometimes called “online behavioral advertising” or “interest-based advertising” or “OBA”).  We also use web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising.  Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Website, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Website and to deliver more relevant advertising. 

In addition, our advertisers or other third parties may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on the Website and other websites.  We do not control the data collection and use practices of these other third parties. You should read the privacy notices of the websites you visit in order to determine what companies may be collecting information on those websites. 

**OBA Opt Out**

If you would like to “opt-out” of being served OBA on the Website by our third-party advertising companies, click on the Ad Choices icon below and select the companies whose OBA technology you would like to block on the Website. 

You may also “opt-out” of other third party programs using OBA technology on your web browser: (a) for users targeted in the United States by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>  and (b) for users targeted in Europe by visiting [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/), selecting the country where you are located, and selecting “Your Ad Choices”. 

**Notification Procedures**

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our Website page, as determined by Company in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time.  Please check this page periodically for changes.  Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes to these terms will constitute acceptance of those changes.  Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and law that applied at the time the information was collected. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at legal [at] EvolveMediaCorp.com, or send mail to: 

Evolve Media Corp. 

5140 W. Goldleaf Circle, 3rd Floor 

Los Angeles, CA  90056 

Attn:  General Counsel
